g-plans.com 2019-06-07

# Survey Complete | G-Plan

### Goglia Nutrition- Privacy Policy

Last Updated: September 18, 2018

By accessing our Services or installing our mobile application, you accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and the processing of your personal data.

Personal data controller  
Responsible for the processing of your personal data is:

COMPANY NAME  
Goglia Nutrition, LLC  
PO Box Box:   
Goglia Nutrition, LLC = G-PLANS.COM  
13508 Van Nuys Blvd #4902 Pacoima, CA. 91333-4902

Information about personal data we collect

Goglia Nutrition, LLC collects information about you in these ways:

Order information you give us: If you place an online order, our secure order form requests contact, billing, and financial information (such as your credit card numbers for purchases). Contact information from the order form (email address, name, billing and shipping address, and phone number) is used to send orders and information about our company to you.

Account information

If you choose to create a Goglia Nutrition, LLC account, your login information is stored with any other information you associate with your account, such as: your email address, first and last name, height, weight, gender.

Moreover,when you use the G-plans Services you regularly upload personal data onto your account such as, depending on your use of the Services; your calorie intake, weight loss goal/weight gain goal, activity/diet routines, your body measurements.

In an ongoing effort to improve our Services, additional personal data may be collected from you. In such cases, we will notify you when the personal data collection takes place.

Our use of your personal data

Your privacy is important to us and we will only process your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy and relevant personal data regulation.

Data processing necessary to provide the Services

As a part of offering the Services to you we process your personal data that you provide us with at the time of registration, such as:

First and last name  
E-mail  
Weight  
Height  
Device identifier, i.e. information on what device, IP-address etc you use to register and log on to the Services

As you continue to use the Services, you will regularly provide G-Plans with further personal data. It follows from the nature of the Services that we must process such data that you upload to the Services to enable the Services, for example, we will process your weight data and calorie intake to enable the monitoring and presentation of your personal goals (whether it be weight loss or weight gain). This processing is a pre-requisite for us being able to offer the Services to you.  

If you connect to the Services using a Third-Party Application (e.g.Facebook) G-Plans will collect and use your personal information from such Third Party Applications such as your name, email address.  

Mobile information

When you access Goglia Nutrition, LLC resources through your iPhone® or Android® phone apps, we may receive non-personally identifiable information, such as a unique identifier for your device letting us know what type of phone you are using.

Cookies

Like most websites, Goglia Nutrition, LLC utilizes cookies. Cookies are a mechanism to remember information about you when you navigate from one web page to another. Our website uses cookies to hold a user’s unique session identifiers, allowing us to serve correct information back to the user. Such information includes your shopping cart items, or whether you are logged in. Our website cookies do not hold any personally identifiable information. Goglia Nutrition, LLC may use other similar technologies which allow us to collect non-personally identifiable information about your visit to help us better your experience.

Rectification of personal data

You have the right to request access to and rectification or erasure of your personal data processed by G-Plans. If a request for rectification concerns data that is necessary for G-Plans to offer the Services, such requests will have the effect that your account will be terminated at G-Plans.

If you wish to exercise this right, you can contact us support@g-plans.com and our customer support will delete your account.

Transfer of data

Third-party service providers: Goglia Nutrition, LLC works closely with other companies and individuals to facilitate transactions and better your experience. Examples of third-party service provider services include shipping orders, analyzing data, providing accurate search results and links, affiliate marketing, and newsletters. Any information that Goglia Nutrition, LLC shares with a third-party service provider is done so safely, securely, and under a contractual relationship with that provider to protect your data. These service providers will be considered processors of your personal data.

At times, some of your personal data by may be transferred and processed to processors, as described above, that are established in the United States or other countries (some of which will be outside the EEA). G-Plans will always apply safeguards to protect your personal data from unauthorized disclosure. We may also transfer your personal data in the event that our business (or part of it) is sold, for instance as part of a merger or acquisition. In case of transfer of data to third parties that are outside of the EU or EEA and that do not offer an adequate level of data protection, G-Plans will apply the EU Commission’s model clauses and/or binding corporate rules, or similar instruments/mechanism, for the safeguarding of integrity and security.

In no event does G-Plans transfer personal data to third parties with the right for such parties to use the data other than on behalf of G-Plans.

Portability

You have the right to receive your personal data which you have provided to G-Plans, in accordance with relevant personal data regulation, provided that such request does not adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others.

Complaints

If you have any questions or complaints about our processing of your personal data, you are welcome to contact us at support@g-plans.com. You also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

Security of the personal data we process

Goglia Nutrition, LLC utilizes technologies such as database encryption to ensure the privacy of your personal information. When you make an online purchase, our advanced security technology uses strong secure protocols to send your personal data to us, making it practically impossible for someone to intercept and extract that data. To further protect your information, we utilize state of the art back-end systems and restrict employee access to your information. Any time we share your information with a third party consistent with this Privacy Policy, we utilize technological and contractual safeguards to keep your information safe.

As a general practice, it is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. If using a shared computer, be sure to log out of your account prior to leaving the computer.

Children

If you are under age 13, you are not allowed not submit any personal data through our Services. Further, we encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet use and to help us in enforcing our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide any personal data through our Service without their permission. If you become aware that a child under the age of 13 has submitted personal data to us, please contact us at support@g-plans.com.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

From time to time, it may become necessary to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Therefore, we reserve the right to update and/or modify this Privacy Policy at any time by giving notice to you. Please review this Privacy Policy frequently, and especially before you register an account with us. The date of the last modification is listed at the bottom of this Privacy Policy.

Contact

We will communicate with you by email and notices posted on your mobile device. If you do not wish to receive notices on your mobile device, you can always turn off this service. Please be aware that if you unsubscribe from our mailing list you will still be receiving answers to your questions sent to our support but you will not be receiving promotional emails.

We welcome your feedback regarding our Services. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [ support@g-plans.com](mailto:support@g-plans.com).

Goglia Nutrition Privacy Policy 

Goglia Nutrition, LLC.com is committed to your privacy. This notice serves to help you better understand what information Goglia Nutrition, LLC collects, how it uses that information, and with whom Goglia Nutrition, LLC may share a limited portion of that information with. If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should contact Customer Support by email at [support@g-plans.com](mailto:support@g-plans.com).

Goglia Nutrition, LLC knows that you value your personal information, and we protect your privacy as if it were our own. Goglia Nutrition, LLC’ uses of your information is limited to the ways outlined in this notice, except as required by law and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

What kind of information about me does Goglia Nutrition, LLC collect?

Goglia Nutrition, LLC collects information about you in these ways:

Order information you give us: If you place an online order, our secure order form requests contact, billing, and financial information (such as your credit card numbers for purchases). Contact information from the order form (email address, name, billing and shipping address, and phone number) is used to send orders and information about our company to you.

Account information: If you choose to create a Goglia Nutrition, LLC account, your login information is stored with any other information you associate with your account.

Information we receive automatically: Like most websites, Goglia Nutrition, LLC utilizes cookies. Cookies are a mechanism to remember information about you when you navigate from one web page to another. Our website uses cookies to hold a user’s unique session identifiers, allowing us to serve correct information back to the user. Such information includes your shopping cart items, or whether you are logged in. Our website cookies do not hold any personally identifiable information. Goglia Nutrition, LLC may use other similar technologies which allow us to collect non-personally identifiable information about your visit to help us better your experience.

Mobile information: When you access Goglia Nutrition, LLC resources through your iPhone® or Android® phone apps, we may receive non-personally identifiable information, such as a unique identifier for your device letting us know what type of phone you are using.

How does Goglia Nutrition, LLC use this information?

Goglia Nutrition, LLC uses information collected in these ways:

Order processing and customer service: After placing an online order, your contact information including your email address will be used to get in touch with you should we have questions regarding subscription order or should we need to notify you of the status of your order. Your credit card information is transmitted securely to our third party processing provider in compliance with Payment Card Industry standards. You will automatically be registered to receive our email newsletter, and a confirmation email will be sent to confirm your preferences. In this email, you can choose to either reject or accept the subscription messages. You are able to opt out at any time by following the unsubscribe link found in the email newsletter, or sending an email to [support@g-plans.com](mailto:support@g-plans.com) with the word UNSUBSCRIBE followed by your email address in the subject of the email.

Third-party service providers: Goglia Nutrition, LLC works closely with other companies and individuals to facilitate transactions and better your experience. Examples of third-party service provider services include shipping orders, analyzing data, providing accurate search results and links, affiliate marketing, and newsletters. Any information that Goglia Nutrition, LLC shares with a third-party service provider is done so safely, securely, and under a contractual relationship with that provider to protect your data.

Promotional offers: From time to time we or a service provider acting on our behalf may use your name, email address, and/or mailing address to send you an offer for a Goglia Nutrition, LLC product or service we believe to be of interest to you.

Other information you provide us: Information you provide us for specific offers or services is only used for the limited purpose for which the information is being given. Examples of these offers or services include Refer-A-Friend, Email to a Friend, surveys, coupons, and sweepstakes.

What information can I access or modify?

If you are a registered customer, you may log into your account and view or modify the account information on file, including personally identifiable information, recent orders, payment settings, shopping lists, and Set & Save settings. In order to protect your personal information, only the last four numbers of any saved credit cards are viewable. You can access and modify your email settings at any time through the Unsubscribe or Preferences link in the footer of any email received from Goglia Nutrition, LLC.

How does Goglia Nutrition, LLC secure my information?

Goglia Nutrition, LLC utilizes technologies such as database encryption to ensure the privacy of your personal information. When you make an online purchase, our advanced security technology uses strong secure protocols to send your personal data to us, making it practically impossible for someone to intercept and extract that data. To further protect your information, we utilize state of the art back-end systems and restrict employee access to your information. Any time we share your information with a third party consistent with this Privacy Policy, we utilize technological and contractual safeguards to keep your information safe.

As a general practice, it is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. If using a shared computer, be sure to log out of your account prior to leaving the computer.

Return Policy

In order to obtain your full refund, contact customer service by email and obtain an RMA (Return Merchandise Authorization) number to place on your package. Write this number on the outside of the shipping package, and send the product back to our fulfillment center at the address listed below, within thirty (30) days of the date you originally ordered the product. In order for your full refund to be processed the product must arrive at our fulfillment facility within thirty (30) days of the original purchase date. You must pay for return shipping. There is a $5.95 restocking fee per unit you are returning. This fee will be taken out of the refund issued. Once our fulfillment center has received the package and relayed the correct information to us, you will be issued a refund.Your refund will be credited back to your bank account, and may take up to 3-5 business days to show in your statement, depending on the speed of the processing bank.

Can I opt-out?

At any time you can adjust your communication preferences, including opting out of promotional mailings, through a preference link in the footer of an email you receive from Goglia Nutrition, LLC. You additionally have the right to remove your account, and any personally identifiable information associated with it, from the Goglia Nutrition, LLC database. To do so, or for more information on this or any other privacy concern, you may email Customer Service. [support@g-plans.com](mailto:support@g-plans.com).
